module.exports = {
    name: 'Quiz 2',
    type: 'multiple choice',
    problems: [
        {
            question: 'When can you turn left against a solid red light?',
            a: 'When you are turning from a two way street to a one way street',
            b: 'When you are turning from a one way street to a two way street',
            c: 'When you are turning from a one way street to a one way street',
            d: 'When you are turning from a two way street to a two way street',
            answer: 'When you are turning from a one way street to a one way street'
        },
        {
            question: 'What does a red curb mean?',
            a: 'Do not park at that curb',
            b: 'You must park at that curb with a time limit',
            c: 'You are only to drop off passengers at that curb',
            d: 'You can park at that curb',
            answer: 'Do not park at that curb'
        },
        {
            question: 'What is the speed limit when driving on the free way?',
            a: '55mph',
            b: '60mph',
            c: '65mph',
            d: '70mph',
            answer: '65mph'
        },
        {
            question: 'What is the best reason to why you should honk the front car?',
            a: 'Be frustrated with them',
            b: 'To break the car',
            c: 'To joke around',
            d: 'To alert them',
            answer: 'To alert them'
        },
        {
            question: 'What is the correct way to park if your car is facing downhill?',
            a: 'Park your car straight',
            b: 'Park you car with your wheels towards the curb',
            c: 'Park you car with your wheels away from the curb',
            d: 'It is illegal to park facing downhill',
            answer: 'Park you car with your wheels towards the curb'
        },
        {
            question: 'What does the double solid yellow line indicate?',
            a: 'You can pass it',
            b: 'You cannot pass it',
            c: 'You are exiting the road',
            d: 'None of the above',
            answer: 'You cannot pass it'
        },
        {
            question: 'What does the white broken line indicate?',
            a: 'You can pass it',
            b: 'You cannot pass it',
            c: 'You are exiting the road',
            d: 'None of the above',
            answer: 'You can pass it'
        },
        {
            question: 'If someone is calling you while driving, you must:',
            a: 'Answer the call',
            b: 'Send a text message',
            c: 'Send a voice message',
            d: 'Don\'t answer the call',
            answer: 'Don\'t answer the call'
        },
        {
            question: 'When is it legal to watch the police incident?',
            a: 'You are interested with the crime',
            b: 'You currently possess a driver\'s license',
            c: 'You have passengers with you to describe the crime.',
            d: 'None of the above',
            answer: ''
        },
        {
            question: 'What is the speed limit when children are present in the road?',
            a: '20mph',
            b: '25mph',
            c: '30mph',
            d: '35mph',
            answer: '25mph'
        },
        {
            question: 'What is the speed limit when children are present in the road?',
            a: '20mph',
            b: '25mph',
            c: '30mph',
            d: '35mph',
            answer: '25mph'
        },
        {
            question: 'What is the speed limit when children are present in the road?',
            a: '20mph',
            b: '25mph',
            c: '30mph',
            d: '35mph',
            answer: '25mph'
        },
        {
            question: 'What is the speed limit when children are present in the road?',
            a: '20mph',
            b: '25mph',
            c: '30mph',
            d: '35mph',
            answer: '25mph'
        },
        {
            question: 'What is the speed limit when children are present in the road?',
            a: '20mph',
            b: '25mph',
            c: '30mph',
            d: '35mph',
            answer: '25mph'
        },
        {
            question: 'What is the speed limit when children are present in the road?',
            a: '20mph',
            b: '25mph',
            c: '30mph',
            d: '35mph',
            answer: '25mph'
        }
    ]
}